[{"answer": "Classic.  Absolutely classic. Profit from major sales push", "docId": "Notting-Hill.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "Yes, better get me a half.  All I can afford", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "What book", "docId": "Notting-Hill.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "I haven't got a book down my trousers", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "Just incidentally", "docId": "Notting-Hill.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "There never will be, you know, unless you actually clean your clothes", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "Any bit in particular", "docId": "Notting-Hill.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "Ahm right, right, I liked the bit in space very much.  Did you enjoy making  that bit", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "Te identicaste con el personaje que interpretabas", "docId": "Notting-Hill.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "No", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "Working with my friend", "docId": "Notting-Hill.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "my friend", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "But no, I'm sure I can get out of it", "docId": "Notting-Hill.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "You'll be my date at my little sister's birthday party", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "I'm sure it's all right.  My friend my friend is cooking and he's acknowledged to be the worst cook in the world, but you know, you could hide the food in your handbag or something", "docId": "Notting-Hill.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "Okay", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "'No comment' means 'yes.", "docId": "Notting-Hill.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "Do you ever masturbate", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "It's the hair!  It's to do with the hair", "docId": "Notting-Hill.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "It was an accident", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "Busy tomorrow", "docId": "Notting-Hill.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "I was", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "Nothing", "docId": "Notting-Hill.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "No, I didn't", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "No, you were brillian", "docId": "Notting-Hill.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "I don't know, I'm afraid", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "I'm rash and I'm stupid and what am I doing with you", "docId": "Notting-Hill.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "I don't know either", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "Here we are.  Do you want to come up", "docId": "Notting-Hill.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "There are lots of reasons.  Do you want to come up", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "I'll see what I can do", "docId": "Notting-Hill.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "Absolutely.  Ice cold still water", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "I don't know where to go.  The hotel is surrounded", "docId": "Notting-Hill.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "Thank you.  I'm just in that place for two days", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "Eleven", "docId": "Notting-Hill.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "my friend", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "Definitely.  'You may show the dent at the top of the artist's buttocks", "docId": "Notting-Hill.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "I could have a stunt bottom, yes", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "How are you doing", "docId": "Notting-Hill.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "I don't know what happened", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": "Yes", "docId": "Notting-Hill.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": "No, no.  She doesn't", "qsentId": 42}]